Guide to the American Theological Library Association Records - Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Affliated Institutions and Organizations, 1990-2004; Series V
  - Pontifical Biblical Institute, Rome, Italy
    - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 589)
  - Presbyterian Church (USA), Worldwide Ministries Division
    - Global Education Grant, 1995 Jan -1996 Dec (Box 14, Folder 590)
  - Protestant Institute for Mission Studies (PIMS), Hungary
    - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 591)
  - Instituto Superior Evangelical Estudios Teologicos (ISEDET)
    - Correspondence regarding early plans for a Latin American Theological Information Network, 1990 Jul -1992 Aug (Box 14, Folder 592)
    - Planning for Bibliografia Teologia Comentada (BTC), 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 593)
    - Planning for Bibliografia Teologia Comentada (BTC), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 594)
    - Planning for Bibliografia Teologia Comentada (BTC), 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 595)
  - Red Latinoamericano de Informacion Teologica (RLIT; formerly ISEDET)
    - ATLA Assistance With Expenses of Boletin del Bibliotecario Teologico Latinoamericano, Correspondence and Newsletters, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 596)
  - Seminario Biblico Latinoamericano (SBL)
    - Correspondence Regarding Potential Areas of Partnership with ATLA, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 597)
  - South Pacific Association of Theological Schools (SPATS)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 598)
  - Universitätsbibliothek Tübingen
    - Correspondence Regarding Partnerships Between Zeitschrifteninhaltsdienst Theologie (ZID) and ATLA, 1990-1997 (Box 14, Folder 599)
    - Correspondence Regarding Partnerships Between Zeitschrifteninhaltsdienst Theologie (ZID) and ATLA, 1990-1997 (Box 14, Folder 600)
  - University of South Africa (UNISA)
    - Correspondence Regarding the South African Theological Bibliography (SATB), 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 601)
  - World Conference of Associations of Theological Institutions (WOCATI)
    - Correspondence Regarding an Article on ATLA for the "WOCATI News", 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 602)
- Regional Groups, 1987-1993; Series VI
  - General
    - 1987 List of Regional Theological Library Associations and correspondence regarding, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 603)
    - Lists, 1987-1997 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Association of Chicago Theological Schools (ACTS)
    - Directory, minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Boston Theological Institute (BTI)
    - Brochure, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Chicago Area Theological Library Association (CATLA)
    - Correspondence, Announcements, and Newsletters, 1991 Jan -1993 Jan (Box 14, Folder 604)
    - Minutes, newsletters, 1994-2000 (Box 17, Folder 36-40)
  - Minnesota Theological Library Association (MTLA)
    - Minutes, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Ohio Theological Library Association (OTLA)
    - Workshop, meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Southeastern Pennsylvania Theological Library Association (SEPTLA)
    - Teamwork Newsletter, 1991 Apr (Box 14, Folder 605)
    - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1992 Oct -1993 Apr (Box 14, Folder 606)
    - Brochure, newsletters, 1994-1999 (Box 17, Folder 43-44)
  - Southwest Area Theological Library Association (SWATLA)
    - SWATLA Newsletter, 1991 Jan 23 (Box 14, Folder 607)
    - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1993 Jan-Jul (Box 14, Folder 608)
    - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 45-47)
  - Tennessee Theological Library Association (TTLA)
    - Workshop report, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 48)